Long ago, this land w as
once cal led Ne verland .
lt w as a beautiful parad ise
w ith abundant g reenery.
H umans, demons, and gods w ere
al l eq ual ly feared and respected
i n this vi rg i n land .
But as ti me passed ,
the w orld found itself fig hti ng
o ver i ncreasi ng pow er.
The Ne verland War took o ver
tw enty mi l l ion l ives.
l n the gg 7 th y ear of the
Demon Century,
a lone hero captured the Tenmak en.
No one had e ver i mag i ned
that such an e vent
w ould trigger another outbreak of
the Ne verland War.
What's this?
The forest is afraid .
S o, this is the sw ord that can destroy
the Demon Ki ng J anus,
the Tenmak en.
l p pushi roia cannot hold the
battle l i ne and is i n retreat.
S hal l w e pursue them?
lt has not been found y et.
We must block the Rig hteous
Army for now.
l 'l l organize a unit for pursuit.
Where's H i ro? Where is she?
Pri ncess H i ro has gone to tak e care
of the old monster that settled
i n the cany on gorge.
You let her go alone?
Did n't w e decide that, once
the battle w as o ver,
w e'd ex orcise it together?
Yes, but. . . Lady Prana!
S ister? !
Where's Father?
H e's resti ng after the battle.
Father and l both thi nk it's
too soon for y ou to fig ht.
Please understand .
l know, but it's more pai nful
for me not to fig ht.
You can't possi bly understand , S ister.
This is such a g reat op portunity ! Drat !
Where'd that N i nja creep go? !
We'l l miss out on this
chance of a l ifeti me.
Zaky o, hel p me look for hi m !
lf y ou get too panick ed , y ou'l l
look l i k e a fool , l ittle boy.
Wel l , it'd be y our fault, S ato !
Where the hel l are y ou?
That should fi nish thi ngs off.
l don't sense any more
mal icious spi rits.
lt's a w aste to hi re mercenaries l i k e us
for such a si mple mission,
rig ht, Pri ncess? !
May be.
Let's get goi ng .
But aren't these spi rits y our al l ies?
The spi rits here are either deserters
or nig ht prow lers.
They're more l i k ely to be
y our associates.
That's a bit harsh.
We're mercenaries.
We mak e a l ivi ng w ith
our fig hti ng ski l ls.
We'l l accept any job,
as long as they acknow ledge
our ski l ls.
You sure y ou're al l rig ht w ith this?
You know, Pri ncess, y our sister
hi red us to protect y ou,
but fig hti ng these losers doesn't
e ven come close
to earni ng w hat w e've been paid .
No kidd i ng . We're pros.
We can't accept that ki nd of
money for doi ng nothi ng .
Then, do as y ou please. Farew el l .
S he's a cold fish.
S omethi ng's not rig ht here.
What w as my sister thi nki ng?
S he w as so cal m,
but then she suddenly cal led i n
these mercenaries.
l 'm entrusti ng y ou w ith this, H i ro.
Why w ould she suddenly send me off
to the Western Forest w ith
these mercenaries?
S he's ne ver done anythi ng
l i k e this before.
Was l j ust i n the w ay?
That could n't be.
You demons w ho defi le the earth,
see if y ou can w ithstand the
sacred l ig ht of this sw ord !
Chiffon !
l 'm fi ne. Come on. We've got to hurry.
l sense them.
The g uerri l la forces from the Rig hteous
Army ha ve fi nal ly come.
lf only the units w e sent
i n pursuit w ere back,
but this ti me, they w on't
return q uickly enoug h.
S o, they ha ve the sw ord?
That most pow erful of al l sw ords,
the Tenmak en.
That's a fancy scythe y ou got there.
Anythi ng special?
The Gate of H ea ven.
lt cuts the soul aw ay, al low i ng
it to rise to H ea ven.
lt's my sister's fa vorite w eapon.
Did y ou hear that? lt's the. . .
l 'd been w onderi ng about it. The only
ones w ho can use such thi ngs
are either the Gods of Death
or the Demon Ki ngs.
S o, w hat's that mean?
S he's either a God of Death
or a Demon Ki ng?
With a face l i k e that?
Yeah, but that's a major scythe.
lt's got to be sacred .
And her monster-l i k e left
hand bothers me too.
S o, Pri ncess, w ho the heck are y ou?
l 'm the Demon Ki ng J anus's
second daug hter, H i ro.
Did n't my sister tel l y ou?
We had no idea!
S o she w as entrusted to us
by order of the G reat Ki ng .
No w onder w e w ere
paid so generously.
But it's strange. Why w ould they
hi re mercenaries
l i k e us to protect the Pri ncess?
Let's go back to the castle.
l ha ve a bad feel i ng .
The castle !
Amazi ng ! l s it some ki nd of explosive?
No, explosives don't
g low l i k e that.
lt has to be a ki nd of sorcery,
some very pow erful mag ic.
Watch out, Pri ncess. There's
somethi ng underfoot.
What's this? lt's huge !
l don't w hat y ou're doi ng here now,
but l 'm i n a hurry,
so get out of my w ay or
l 'l l cut y ou to pieces !
S ato !
lt'l l tak e more than that !
They're fi nal ly here.
lf it's the last thi ng l do,
l must seal the sw ord ,
the Tenmak en, aw ay.
That sw ord is the most pow erful
sw ord i n the w orld ,
created by the gods solely for
my destruction.
lt holds the most pow erful
forces of the hea vens.
The gods know no bounds w hen
it comes to those they hate.
They've alw ay s been that w ay.
l mag i ne w hat w ould hap pen
if either humans or demons,
w ith thei r end less desi res,
e ver obtai ned that dangerous
sw ord created by the gods? !
Not only w ould l be ki l led , but
the w orld w ould be destroy ed .
We're here.
Demon Ki ng J anus !
For the sak e of al l humanity,
w e're goi ng to destroy y ou !
Go on. S how me w hat y ou've got.
l w i l l be sw al low ed up w ith pow er
eq ual to that of my si ns.
What do w e do next?
This abi l ity to i nstantly
heal any i nj ury. . .
These pow ers of regeneration are
somethi ng to be reck oned w ith.
Damn ! l ha ve to get the Pri ncess
back to the castle,
but this one is awful ly fast
for such a big creature.
Even if the Pri ncess escapes,
it can sti l l catch up w ith her.
l ha ve no choice.
l 'l l tak e her back to the castle
usi ng my N i nja techniq ue.
Keep hi m there, e ven if
it's only for a second .
No ! l can't lea ve y ou tw o behi nd .
What are y ou say i ng? Don't
underesti mate us, Pri ncess.
l could tak e this beast by my self!
H old on tig ht, Pri ncess.
We're goi ng to fly !
You g uy s. . .
Tak e these blood-coag ulati ng bul lets !
Now's y our chance. Go !
Gen tousha kaij i n retsu zai zen. . .
We'l l mak e it to the castle i n one shot !
Moon N i nja techniq ue, S hadow Run !
Al l rig ht !
Whoa! Now w e ha ve to
fi nish this g uy off.
Father!
Now it's y our turn to rule
the w orld , humans.
O nce the pow er of my
dark i nfl uence fades,
the pow ers of the monsters
should w eak en as w el l ,
and may be the chaos i n
the w orld w i l l d isap pear.
But l w i l l tak e this sw ord w ith me,
to seal eternal ly i n
the other w orld .
S ee w hat y ou can do on y our ow n.
Now, w i l l y ou be able
to protect this w orld?
Father!
H i ro. . .
S ister!
H i ro, l 'm sorry ! l 'm so sorry
l could n't tel l y ou.
We made y ou lea ve because w e knew
that they w ere comi ng
w ith the Tenmak en.
But w hy? Why are y ou o ver there?
lf our father's dead
spi rit is left alone,
it w i l l turn i nto an e vi l spi rit.
S trong spi rits l i k e his
req ui re more
than j ust a reg ular God
of Death for passage.
lt req ui res someone w ith
stronger pow ers.
S o, y ou sacrificed y ourself? !
No ! Why d id y ou lea ve
me al l alone? !
l ask one last fa vor.
l need y ou to cut my spi rit free
w ith the Gate of H ea ven.
No ! l could n't !
Pri ncess, no, Miss H i ro, y ou can.
lf y ou don't do it, w ho w i l l? !
Your sister's only w ish
w as for y ou to l ive.
l mag i ne how pai nful it w as for her,
to ha ve to k eep this to herself,
to ne ver say good by e.
Become strong , H i ro.
Chiffon !
S orry to ha ve k ept y ou w aiti ng !
Wel l , w asn't that q uick?
What, that thi ng? Piece of cak e.
The Demon Ki ng J anus is dead !
Retreat, now.
Yes !
The w orld is goi ng to
col lapse i nto chaos.
The fi ne balance that my father
mai ntai ned throug h fear
has been destroy ed .
Now humans e veryw here w i l l rise
up to try to clai m the throne.
l don't bel ie ve humans w i l l be able
to rule the w orld w el l at fi rst.
H umans rely on the gods too much.
Demons ha ve alw ay s ruled the w orld .
l bel ie ve they should sti l l rule.
l 'm not an i ntel lectual or anythi ng ,
so l can't say much,
but l 'l l stick w ith y ou.
Besides, l sti l l ha ven't
earned my fee y et.
S ouls from the other w orld ,
bri ng forth pow er i nto this w orld .
Die? !
H ow many bi rthday s has it
been si nce w e've met?
S oon, it w i l l be ti me for the
angels to descend
l w ant to gaze at y our face as y ou
hand le the steeri ng w heel
Because the ti me w hen w e fel l i n
lo ve is reflected i n y our ey es
We'l l pass throug h the tunnel of stars,
and i n our reg ular place
S ti l l al l day long
l w i l l stay by y our side
Long ago, this land w as
cal led Ne verland .
lt w as a mag nificent parad ise w ith
an abundance of g reenery.
lt w as vi rg i n territory w here
humans, demons, and gods
w ere al l eq ual ly respected and feared .
As ti me passed , the w orld fel l
i nto a strugg le o ver pow er.
l n the gg 7 th y ear of the
Demon Century,
a hero named Chiffon
obtai ned the Tenmak en,
a sw ord w hich humans perhaps
ne ver should ha ve d raw n.
The Demon Ki ng J anus, w ho
had reig ned o ver the land ,
w as destroy ed by the pow er
of the Tenmak en.
Command of the Demon Forces fel l
to the y oung Pri ncess H i ro.
But pow erful nations could not
ig nore such a chance.
l w as born of the union betw een
a human and a demon.
H i ro !
May mee. . .
lt's the chi ld of a demon !
Ki l l her!
A demon chi ld !
Die !
Ki l l !
Ki l l her!
The situation is extremely serious.
The news of the Demon
Ki ng J anus' death
at the hand of the hero Chiffon
has spread w orldw ide.
l n a desi re to tak e
o ver his throne,
the humans are plotti ng to destroy
the remai ni ng Demon Forces.
J ust the countries that are clearly
mobi l izi ng forces are :
H el l hanpool's Vang le Band its,
Logeon's Flauster Forces,
the Muromachi Army,
the S i l i neeg Knig hts,
S un Rio's Mi l l ia Forces, and
AX's Dome Battle Force.
No new ly reformed Demon Forces
could w ithstand that ki nd
of an onslaug ht.
l n other w ords. . .
l n other w ords, the demon race
itself is i n danger of exti nction.
Why? Why d id my father ha ve
to d ie, Bai rd the 1 3th?
You could say it w as j ust the ti mes.
The Demon Ki ng J anus
w as too pow erful .
The humans bel ie ved J anus
control led al l the demons.
That may ha ve been true, but i n real ity
no one could rule the people
w ith fear alone.
You could say J anus o verstep ped
his position.
Bastard ! This from the second i n
command of the Demon Forces? !
S o, w hat do y ou propose w e do?
A number of human nations are
w i l l i ng to form an al l iance.
Why not joi n forces w ith them?
That w ay the humans w on't
be so q uick to attack.
There is no such country !
H umans and demons
together? ! l mpossi ble !
You're w rong , Pri ncess.
A number of countries ha ve al ready
d ispatched envoy s
to meet w ith me, out of respect
for my leadershi p.
You're bei ng mani pulated .
H i ro, l understand w hy y ou
don't trust the humans.
l w as there the day y ou
lost y our arm,
but to lose so many l ives
o ver it doesn't. . .
May mee, our enemies'
desi re is to d ivide us,
so that they can then destroy us.
l don't care if al l the Demon
Forces d isap pear,
if it w i l l bri ng peace.
May mee. . .
Bai rd the 1 3th, l am not fi nished !
Your w ish is my command , Pri ncess.
l 'm a human too, Pri ncess !
Charge !
Let's go !
Rig ht !
Where the hel l is Bai rd? !
Chick, send the sig nal !
l s that so? The new ly formed
Demon Forces w ere. . .
Yes, S i r. Even if they can
defeat the Black Knig hts,
the l p pushi roia Forces
are rig ht behi nd them.
The Demon Ki ng had a daug hter,
but there is d isag reement o ver
w ho shal l sit on the throne.
Thei r defeat is only
a matter of ti me.
l al ready know that, but there are
al l ki nds of demons.
S ome fools e ven thi nk they're
the same as humans.
J addo, are y ou planni ng to
ki l l off the demon race too?
Don't y ou thi nk a fool ish demon is no
better than the a verage human? !
Fools !
Pri ncess Little S now ! Rejoice !
O ur ti me has fi nal ly come.
There y ou are.
J addo !
With al l the pow er w e've amassed ,
w e'l l soon rule Ne verland .
Wi l l the w orld be a better place?
Yes, of course. lt'l l be a w orld w ith
one genui nely superior race.
l s there anythi ng l can do
to assist y ou, J addo?
That's w hy l had y ou summoned ,
to tak e the throne.
l . . .
w ant to hel p y ou.
lt's a mi racle. lt's the only explanation.
You're rig ht. That w as w ay too close.
lf they had n't retreated because
of Zaki phon's bra vado,
w e'd ha ve been creamed .
With Zaki phon critical ly w ounded
and unable to fig ht,
and only a hund red recruits left, w hat
do y ou w ant to do, Pri ncess?
lt's ti me that y ou told us w hy y our
rei nforcements w ere late.
My father has his ow n ideas.
lf w e had sent more troops
i nto that chaos,
our casual ities w ould ha ve
been e ven g reater.
S orry.
For now, it'd be w ise to
fol low Bai rd's plan.
l d id n't joi n the Demon Army
j ust to get my self ki l led .
That's because y ou're a human.
lt's not surprisi ng that y ou'd
betray the demons.
S o, go. Go on back to the humans.
You hard-headed , stubborn fool !
H ey ! Chick! Wait !
You know y ou can go too,
if y ou w ant.
The only one hung up on humans
and demons is y ou, Pri ncess !
Do y ou ha ve a plan?
H ow could l ? But as it is, w e'l l d ie.
Chick, y ou. . .
S ato, stay here w ith the
Pri ncess and Zaki phon.
O ne traitor is enoug h.
Chick.
l 'm counti ng on y ou, Chick!
Dad !
l 'm okay. S tay put.
Yes.
H ow can l send my troops i n
w ithout any proof that y ou are
an official envoy?
Azalea, Pri ncess of the
Deep Forest Elves,
d uri ng my tra vels, l heard of y our
ad mi nistration's pol icies,
that y ou are seeki ng peace,
that y ou are w i l l i ng to fig ht to
protect the beauty of the land .
And so?
H i ro, the Q ueen of the new ly
formed Demon Forces,
isn't someone w ho desi res w ar.
l n her position as the hei r
to the Demon Ki ng J anus,
she has been forced i nto battle,
but her desi re is the same as
y ours, Pri ncess Azalea.
Envoy from a faraw ay
land , w hat is peace?
The beauty of this forest doesn't
come from peace.
l n order to reap the
blessi ngs of nature,
there is much w e ha ve to do.
lf w e can only reap a harvest
after w e plant the fields,
can that sti l l be cal led nature?
l don't understand w hat y ou mean.
What it means is that l can't i mag i ne
that the demon throne thi nks the
same w ay as l do.
But. . .
Answ er my q uestion, please.
Where is the proof that y ou are the
official envoy of the demons?
l can get proof,
but w e must hurry.
lf the new ly formed Demon Forces fal l ,
the humans w i l l ha ve an al l-out
w ar for domi nance,
and another Ne verland
War w i l l occur.
l 've been l isteni ng
for a w hi le now.
H umans this and humans that. . .
But aren't y ou a human too? !
Wel l , the l ittle boy fig hts i mpressively.
l l i k e y ou !
Reig ni ng Ki ng of Muromachi ,
O rochi-maru !
You thi nk y ou can sneak i nto my
castle and get aw ay w ith it? !
S o, y ou've heard of me.
l g uess it's paid off bei ng
ki nd to the l ittle elf babes.
Your careless beha vior is w el l
know n e veryw here.
S o, w hy are y ou here?
lt mak es my blood boi l .
O ne si mple al l iance could determi ne
one's fate for eternity.
S tay back! You're no match for hi m.
Very cle ver, Your H ig hness
of the Forest.
Your sold iers w ho tried to stop me
en route w ere w orthless too.
lf y ou do as he req uests, and
assist the Demon Forces,
l 'l l add my rei nforcements too,
j ust this once.
What?
lf w e let the l p pushi roia gai n
too much pow er now,
there's no turni ng back.
That w on't be very amusi ng
for either of us.
Pri ncess Azalea!
l ha ve no i ntention of
fig hti ng for y ou !
Wel l , that's a bit harsh. Feel i ng
a bit neurotic today?
Please, Pri ncess Azalea,
please reconsider!
l mag i ne w hat w i l l hap pen if humans
that can only thi nk of themselves
rule the w orld !
l understand that. But fig hti ng
resolves nothi ng .
l sn't there anythi ng else
l can negotiate w ith?
Listen up ! The enemy is at the
castle j ust o ver the border.
Protect the border w ith y our l ife.
S how them the Demon
Forces' determi nation !
Wel l , w e're off.
Looks l i k e Chick d id n't mak e it i n ti me.
Why d id y ou lea ve me al l alone?
Father? S ister? The throne is
too much for me.
We must fig ht agai nst the Demon
Ki ng's remai ni ng hei r now.
l don't know any more.
Must w e destroy al l the demons?
H umans need to be go verned
by the proper leaders.
l n an ideal w orld , demons
are unnecessary !
What is it, Chiffon? Why such a
g l um face rig ht before battle?
What? Nothi ng .
Chiffon, do y ou feel it too?
l don't know w hat it is, but
l ha ve a real ly bad feel i ng .
l s the Demon Army near?
Did they see us?
Go !
lt's an ambush !
Don't panic ! There aren't
many of them !
lt's an ambush !
Don't panic ! There aren't
many of them !
Are y ou okay, Ranjay?
No. The e vi l's e ven stronger now.
Amazi ng !
Daug hter of the Demon Ki ng !
Where are y ou? !
S o, at last w e meet,
my l ittle sister.
Who are y ou?
My name is J addo.
J addo? l 've ne ver heard of y ou.
J anus banished me.
Feari ng l mig ht become
more pow erful than he,
the father abandoned the son.
But l w on't abandon y ou.
l ha ve the Platee S i lver
Forces behi nd me.
Now, al l that remai ns is for y ou to
hand the throne o ver to me.
Why w ould l hand y ou the throne,
w hen Father refused
to g ive it to y ou?
You only w ant the throne for
y our ow n personal gai n.
l 'm on the throne to fig ht for
those w ho bel ie ve i n me.
Then w hy don't y ou d ie
rig ht here for them? !
Pri ncess !
Desperate Muscle !
You tal k a good l i ne,
but y our hand is proof
of the w orld's hate !
Good . Now that the w ei rd
one is gone. . .
Traitor! A human w orki ng
for a demon.
lt's traitors l i k e y ou that
confuse men's hearts !
lt's self-rig hteous fools l i k e y ou
that j ump to concl usions !
Pri ncess ! S ato !
l s that Chick? ! We're sa ved !
lt's the enemy ! The enemy !
Damn ! Retreat ! Retreat !
lf w e had n't been i nterrupted ,
w e'd ha ve w on.
l 'm sorry, J addo.
With my current strength, l can't
e ven control my ow n pow ers.
H i ro, l 'l l mak e y ou
understand e ventual ly.
S omehow, w e made it i n ti me.
You had me w orried
there for a w hi le.
You d id w el l . Thank y ou !
Please don't thank me.
l ig nored y our orders.
l w as w rong .
Pri ncess, actual ly. . .
Are y ou the leader of the new ly
formed Demon Forces?
Pri ncess, actual ly. . .
Are y ou the leader of the new ly
formed Demon Forces?
You ha ve good men servi ng y ou.
l offered my sup port i n ex change
for his ag reement to enter my service.
At this ti me, l w i l l transfer his service
to y ou, if y ou don't mi nd .
You sure about this?
They could become y our w orst
enemies someday.
l ha ve no i nterest i n seei ng
the forest burn.
Al l l w ant to do now is go home.
You had better go back to Muromachi
before l ki l l y ou.
l ne ver know w hat that elf is thi nki ng .
H umans and demons al i k e.
l w i l l trust y ou al l .
Amidst a w hi rlw i nd of emotions, H i ro,
ha vi ng at last found somethi ng
to bel ie ve i n,
has tak en the fi rst step tow ard
securi ng her throne.
Deatte nandome no anata no H ap p y
Bi rthday
Ato suk oshi de tenshitachi
oritekuru j i kan ne
H andoru furu anata no y ok ogao
sotto mitsumetai kara
Koishitak oro hitomi ni utsuruy o
H oshi no tonneru o kug utte,
itsumono tok oro de
Watashi w a ichi nichij uu
S oba ni ite ageru
[ Skipped item nr. 478 ]
[ Skipped item nr. 479 ]
[ Skipped item nr. 480 ]
[ Skipped item nr. 481 ]